flamingoworld.com 2004-12-04

# Free Online Coupons and Coupon Codes, Discounts and Sales at FlamingoWorld.com

**Effective February 18, 2004**

**Our Privacy Policy**   

FlamingoWorld.com (http://www.flamingoworld.com) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from our users. Please read the following to understand our views and practices regarding personal information, and how they pertain to you as you use our various features and services. This statement discloses the current privacy practices for our Web sites.  
There are no legal disclaimer statements (i.e., terms and conditions, etc.) on FlamingoWorld that contradict the promises made in our privacy notice.   
If we make any substantive changes to this policy, we'll announce it on our site.   

Regardless of later updates or changes to our privacy notice, we will never use the information you submit under our current privacy notice in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. 

**What Information Does FlamingoWorld.com Gather About You?**   
FlamingoWorld.com collects a limited amount of information about our visitors in order to send emails and provide access to our forum.   
We may ask for your name and email address in order to register you to use our bulletin board, personalized deal listing, and/or newsletter subscription. We also may ask for your name and address if you win sweepstakes or other promotions sponsored by FlamingoWorld.com in order to mail you your prize. If you win a contest we will not save that information after your prize is sent, nor will we share it with anyone. We will never use your information for any other purposes.

**Use of "Cookies"**  
If your browser is set up to accept them, our bulletin boards use a feature known as a "cookie." Our forums use cookies which are associated with your email address. Cookies are used to automatically access your previously stored account preferences when you log in to our forums. These are used only when you log in and are only used to log you in to your account so you may change information and post in our forums. When you log out of your account in the forums, all personally identifiable information is removed from the cookies.  
Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when you've d one. If you reject cookies, though, you will not be able to use certain areas of our site. Even if you accept our cookies, unless you tell us, we cannot find out who you are. 

**How Does FlamingoWorld.com Use Your Personal Information?**   
FlamingoWorld.com collects personal information to provide you, the user, with the best and most personalized Web experience possible. We use that information to send you email newsletters and deal alerts. All emails, newsletters etc. will include special instructions in them to unsubscribe.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.  
**All users may at any time opt-out of our marketing by the following methods:**  

Our newsletters include a link at the bottom to click on to automatically unsubscribe you.  
To opt out of our Forums and Emails, log in to your account here:  

http://www.flamingoworld.com/forum/login.php and in your main configuration area you have the option to opt out and or unsubscribe at any time.

**Will We Disclose Any of Your Personal Information?**   
flamingoworld.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We do not provide individual information to our advertisers. We will occassionally provide general demographic information of our site to perspective advertisers. For example, we might tell our advertiser that out of our 100,000 subscribers, 20,000 of which are female living in San Francisco. The advertiser will never know that Mary is one of them and she is a female lives in San Francisco.   
We will only disclose your personal information when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information; 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
  * We explicitly specify that we will be sharing your information, such in the case of joint promotion, sweepstakes, or giveaways. 

**What If I Link to a Third-Party Web Site?**   
This site contains links to other sites. flamingoworld.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites, although we do try to only place links to sites that have privacy notices.  
When you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, FlamingoWorld.com cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can access to review all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your account at http://www.flamingoworld.com/forum/login.php. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Who has access to your information?  
**No one has access to your information given to FlamingoWorld except you and FlamingoWorld.com. No outside contractors or agent of FlamingoWorld will ever have access to your information. All your information is password protected and cannot be accessed by anyone but you or FlamingoWorld.com.

**How To Contact Us**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [contact@flamingoworld.com](mailto:contact@flamingoworld.com)
